Guide to the Cecily Brownstone Papers MSS.134
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XII: Recipe Box Collection
  - Unidentified painted recipe box. Contains index of various cookbooks and published recipes., undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_61eaa6643cb2f7fdb53b72702810e574)
  - Unidentified, wooden recipe box. Contains index of various cookbooks published recipes., undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_5683b2a9457f4d22fe4c0ce86c56bdb1)
- Series XIII: Pamphlet Collection
  A portion of these pamphlets were culled from the Cecile Brownstone cookbook collection. The arrangement of pamphlets reflects Cecile's original categorization, except for headings in brackets which were designated by Fales.
  - Pamphlet classification scheme, [1996] (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Presidents, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Railroad, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Shaker, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - U.S.A regional, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - [U.S.A. regional (2)], undated (Box 15, Folder 5A)
  - Maryland, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - New England, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - New Jersey, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - New York (1 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - New York (2 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - New York (3 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania (1 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Pennsylvania (2 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Florida, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Hawaii, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Southern, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Southwestern, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Wisconsin, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - New York Public Library (1 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - New York Public Library (2 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Auctions, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - [A&P Menus], undated (Box 15, Folder 21A)
  - Bob Brown Books, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Crahan, Elizabeth, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Gernon, John Talbot, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Gore, Marian, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Einhorn Maxwell Books, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Caughren, Kay, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - [Cookbook Materials], undated (Box 16, Folder 27A)
  - Corner Book Shop, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - [Cooking Courses], undated (Box 16, Folder 28A)
  - Dealers, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Fillin, Lucille, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - General foods, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Longone, Jan (1 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Longone, Jan (2 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - McKirdy, T., undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Powell's Books for Cooks, undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Scruggs, Thomas [Mrs.], undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - [Taylor, MaryLee], undated (Box 16, Folder 36A)
  - Weindling, Barbara, undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Woodburn, Elisabeth (1 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Woodburn, Elizabeth (2 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Fireless cookers, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Aluminum, undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Casseroles, undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Chafing dishes, undated (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Crepes, undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Crockpots, undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Corning, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Cutlery, undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Foley, undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Fondue, undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - [Misc. Cookware], undated (Box 16, Folder 49A)
  - Iron, undated (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Microwave, undated (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Mirro (1 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Mirro (2 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Mixers, undated (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Pressure cookers, undated (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Reynolds, undated (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Roaster oven, undated (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Stainless steel, undated (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Trays-electric, undated (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Electric skillet, undated (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Electric wok, undated (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Farberware, undated (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Stoves, undated (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Freezing-government, undated (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Frozen and freezing, undated (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Freezing (1 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Freezing (2 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Foreign (1 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Foreign (2 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Africa, undated (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Belgium, undated (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Canada, undated (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Caribbean, undated (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - China, undated (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Denmark (1 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Denmark (2 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - England, undated (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - France, undated (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Germany, undated (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Greece, undated (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Holland, undated (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Hungary, undated (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - India, undated (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Indian curry recipes, undated (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Italy, undated (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Japan, undated (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Jewish cuisine, undated (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - [Mexico], undated (Box 18, Folder 87A)
  - Middle Eastern cuisine, undated (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Russian, undated (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Scandinavian, undated (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Spain, undated (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Switzerland, undated (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - South American, undated (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - [General Recipes], undated (Box 18, Folder 93A)
  - Cakes, undated (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - Cookies (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - Cookies (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - Outdoors (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - Outdoors (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - Metropolitan (Met) Life, undated (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Coffee (1 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Coffee (2 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Bakers (1 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Bakers (2 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Cocoa and chocolate, undated (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Hershey's, undated (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Nestle's, undated (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Tea, undated (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - [Advice], undated (Box 19, Folder 107A)
  - Appetizers, undated (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - Breakfast, undated (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Budget, undated (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Bride and wedding, undated (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - [Children], undated (Box 19, Folder 111A)
  - Holiday (1 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 112)
  - Holiday (2 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 113)
  - Entertainment, undated (Box 20, Folder 114)
  - Quick cookery, undated (Box 20, Folder 115)
  - Summer, undated (Box 20, Folder 116)
  - Senior years, undated (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Small quantity, undated (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - Quantity (1 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 119)
  - Quantity (2 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 120)
  - Wartime, undated (Box 20, Folder 121)
  - Wrappings, undated (Box 20, Folder 122)
  - Diet (1 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 123)
  - Diet (2 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 124)
  - Aperitif, undated (Box 20, Folder 125)
  - Miscellaneous (mostly wine), undated (Box 21, Folder 126)
  - Miscellaneous (mostly wine), undated (Box 21, Folder 127)
  - American wine, undated (Box 21, Folder 128)
  - California wine, undated (Box 21, Folder 129)
  - Miscellaneous wines and sherries, undated (Box 21, Folder 130)
  - Miscellaneous (mostly alcohol), undated (Box 21, Folder 131)
  - Beverages (non-alcoholic), undated (Box 21, Folder 132)
  - Seagrams, undated (Box 21, Folder 133)
  - Liquor stores, undated (Box 21, Folder 134)
  - Wine (1 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 135)
  - Wine (2 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 136)
  - Wine (3 of 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 137)
  - Beer, undated (Box 21, Folder 138)
  - Cocktails, undated (Box 21, Folder 139)
  - Liqueurs (1 of 2), undated (Box 21, Folder 140)
  - Liqueurs (2 of 2), undated (Box 21, Folder 141)
  - Whiskey, undated (Box 21, Folder 142)
  - Southern Comfort, undated (Box 21, Folder 143)
  - Bourbon, undated (Box 21, Folder 144)
  - Brandy, undated (Box 21, Folder 145)
  - Champagne, undated (Box 21, Folder 146)
  - Rum, undated (Box 21, Folder 147)
  - Tequila, undated (Box 21, Folder 148)
  - Vodka, undated (Box 21, Folder 149)
  - Baking soda, undated (Box 21, Folder 150)
  - Baking powder, undated (Box 21, Folder 151)
  - Mixes, undated (Box 22, Folder 152)
  - Flour, undated (Box 22, Folder 153)
  - Flour (Robin Hood and Wheat Flour Institute), undated (Box 22, Folder 154)
  - Self-rising flour, undated (Box 22, Folder 155)
  - Yeast Breads, undated (Box 22, Folder 156)
  - Uses of bread, undated (Box 22, Folder 157)
  - Breads (1 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 158)
  - Breads (2 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 159)
  - [Bisquick], undated (Box 22, Folder 159A)
  - Fleischmann's (1 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 160)
  - Fleischmann's (2 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 161)
  - [Pillsbury], undated (Box 22, Folder 161A)
  - Quick bread, undated (Box 22, Folder 162)
  - Red Star Yeast, undated (Box 22, Folder 163)
  - English muffins, undated (Box 22, Folder 164)
  - Pretzels, undated (Box 22, Folder 165)
  - Cookies and crackers, undated (Box 22, Folder 166)
  - Pancakes, crepes, and waffles, undated (Box 22, Folder 167)
  - Sandwiches (1 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 168)
  - Sandwiches (2 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 169)
  - Buckwheat flour and groat, undated (Box 22, Folder 170)
  - Cornmeal and grits, undated (Box 22, Folder 171)
  - Wheat, undated (Box 22, Folder 172)
  - Grains and cereals, undated (Box 22, Folder 173)
  - Wheat germ, undated (Box 22, Folder 174)
  - Kellogg (1 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 175)
  - Kellogg (2 of 2), undated (Box 22, Folder 176)
  - Nabisco, undated (Box 23, Folder 177)
  - Pasta (1 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 178)
  - Pasta (2 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 179)
  - Rice (1 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 180)
  - Rice (2 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 181)
  - Rice companies, undated (Box 23, Folder 182)
  - Wild rice, undated (Box 23, Folder 183)
  - Tapioca, undated (Box 23, Folder 184)
  - Quaker, undated (Box 23, Folder 185)
  - Ralston, undated (Box 23, Folder 186)
  - General foods, undated (Box 23, Folder 187)
  - General foods, undated (Box 23, Folder 188)
  - General foods, undated (Box 23, Folder 189)
  - Swans Down, undated (Box 23, Folder 190)
  - Betty Crocker (1 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 191)
  - Betty Crocker (2 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 192)
  - Mixes, undated (Box 23, Folder 193)
  - Frostings, fillings, toppings, undated (Box 23, Folder 194)
  - Candy, undated (Box 23, Folder 195)
  - Marshmallows, undated (Box 23, Folder 196)
  - Desserts, undated (Box 23, Folder 197)
  - Pastry, undated (Box 23, Folder 198)
  - Pies, undated (Box 23, Folder 199)
  - Mazola (1 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 200)
  - Mazola (2 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 201)
  - Waring, undated (Box 24, Folder 202)
  - Food processors (1 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 203)
  - Food processors (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 204)
  - Ice cream (1 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 205)
  - Ice cream (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 206)
  - Fryers, undated (Box 24, Folder 207)
  - Refrigerators (1 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 208)
  - Refrigerators (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 209)
  - Gas and electric, undated (Box 24, Folder 210)
  - Ranges (1 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 211)
  - Ranges (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 212)
  - Miscellaneous electric and gas housewares, undated (Box 24, Folder 213)
  - Miscellaneous electric and gas housewares, undated (Box 24, Folder 214)
  - Pressure cooker, undated (Box 24, Folder 215)
  - Planter oils and fats, undated (Box 24, Folder 216)
  - Olive oil, undated (Box 24, Folder 217)
  - Crisco, undated (Box 24, Folder 218)
  - Lard, undated (Box 24, Folder 219)
  - Spry, undated (Box 24, Folder 220)
  - Swifts, undated (Box 24, Folder 221)
  - Wesson, undated (Box 24, Folder 222)
  - Dairy and butter, undated (Box 24, Folder 223)
  - Dairy (1 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 224)
  - Dairy (2 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 225)
  - Margarine, undated (Box 25, Folder 226)
  - Cheese (1 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 227)
  - Cheese (2 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 228)
  - Blue cheese, undated (Box 25, Folder 229)
  - Cottage and cheddar cheese, undated (Box 25, Folder 230)
  - Swiss and cream cheese, undated (Box 25, Folder 231)
  - Cream, undated (Box 25, Folder 232)
  - Eggs (1 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 233)
  - Eggs (2 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 234)
  - Eggs (government), undated (Box 25, Folder 235)
  - Yogurt, undated (Box 25, Folder 236)
  - Milk, undated (Box 25, Folder 237)
  - Condensed milk, undated (Box 25, Folder 238)
  - Dry milk, undated (Box 25, Folder 239)
  - Evaporated milk, undated (Box 25, Folder 240)
  - Carnation, undated (Box 25, Folder 241)
  - Armour, undated (Box 25, Folder 242)
  - Swift, undated (Box 25, Folder 243)
  - National Live Stock and Meat Board, undated (Box 25, Folder 244)
  - Beef, undated (Box 25, Folder 245)
  - Ground meat, undated (Box 26, Folder 246)
  - Meat, undated (Box 26, Folder 247)
  - [Meatless], undated (Box 26, Folder 247A)
  - Budget meat, undated (Box 26, Folder 248)
  - Canned meats, undated (Box 26, Folder 249)
  - Frankfurters, undated (Box 26, Folder 250)
  - Ham, undated (Box 26, Folder 251)
  - Lamb (1 of 2), undated (Box 26, Folder 252)
  - Lamb (2 of 2), undated (Box 26, Folder 253)
  - Pork (1 of 2), undated (Box 26, Folder 254)
  - Pork (2 of 2), undated (Box 26, Folder 255)
  - Specialty meats, undated (Box 26, Folder 256)
  - Veal, undated (Box 26, Folder 257)
  - Chicken (1 of 4), undated (Box 26, Folder 258)
  - Chicken (2 of 4), undated (Box 26, Folder 259)
  - Chicken (3 of 4), undated (Box 26, Folder 260)
  - Chicken (4 of 4), undated (Box 26, Folder 261)
  - Poultry, undated (Box 26, Folder 262)
  - Cornish hens, undated (Box 26, Folder 263)
  - Game, undated (Box 26, Folder 264)
  - Goose, undated (Box 26, Folder 265)
  - Turkey (1 of 2), undated (Box 26, Folder 266)
  - Turkey (2 of 2), undated (Box 26, Folder 267)
  - Flavorings, undated (Box 26, Folder 268)
  - Herbs (1 of 3), undated (Box 26, Folder 269)
  - Herbs (2 of 3), undated (Box 26, Folder 270)
  - Herbs (3 of 3), undated (Box 26, Folder 271)
  - House of Herbs, undated (Box 26, Folder 272)
  - Mustard, undated (Box 26, Folder 273)
  - MSG, undated (Box 26, Folder 274)
  - Spices (1 of 4), undated (Box 26, Folder 275)
  - Spices (2 of 4), undated (Box 27, Folder 276)
  - Spices (3 of 4), undated (Box 27, Folder 277)
  - Spices (4 of 4), undated (Box 27, Folder 278)
  - Heinz, undated (Box 27, Folder 279)
  - Seeds, undated (Box 27, Folder 280)
  - Vinegar, undated (Box 27, Folder 281)
  - Seafood (1 of 4), undated (Box 27, Folder 282)
  - Seafood (2 of 4), undated (Box 27, Folder 283)
  - Seafood (3 of 4), undated (Box 27, Folder 284)
  - Seafood (4 of 4), undated (Box 27, Folder 285)
  - Crab, undated (Box 27, Folder 286)
  - Fish (1 of 3), undated (Box 27, Folder 287)
  - Fish (2 of 3), undated (Box 27, Folder 288)
  - Fish (3 of 3), undated (Box 27, Folder 289)
  - Salmon (1 of 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 290)
  - Salmon (2 of 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 291)
  - Sardines, undated (Box 27, Folder 292)
  - Tuna, undated (Box 27, Folder 293)
  - Lobster and clams, undated (Box 27, Folder 294)
  - Pecans, undated (Box 28, Folder 295)
  - Pistachios, undated (Box 28, Folder 296)
  - Walnuts (1 of 2), undated (Box 28, Folder 297)
  - Walnuts (2 of 2), undated (Box 28, Folder 298)
  - Sugar, undated (Box 28, Folder 299)
  - Angostura, undated (Box 28, Folder 300)
  - Mayonnaise, undated (Box 28, Folder 301)
  - Nuts, undated (Box 28, Folder 302)
  - Chestnuts, undated (Box 28, Folder 303)
  - Coconuts, undated (Box 28, Folder 304)
  - Almonds (1 of 2), undated (Box 28, Folder 305)
  - Almonds (2 of 2), undated (Box 28, Folder 306)
  - Macadamia nuts, undated (Box 28, Folder 307)
  - Brazil nuts, undated (Box 28, Folder 308)
  - Peanuts (1 of 2), undated (Box 28, Folder 309)
  - Peanuts (2 of 2), undated (Box 28, Folder 310)
  - Molasses, undated (Box 28, Folder 311)
  - Worcestershire, undated (Box 28, Folder 312)
  - Tabasco, undated (Box 28, Folder 313)
  - [Kikkoman Soy Sauce], undated (Box 28, Folder 313A)
  - Maple sugar and syrup, undated (Box 28, Folder 314)
  - Corn syrup, undated (Box 28, Folder 315)
  - Honey, undated (Box 28, Folder 316)
  - Bouillon (1 of 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 317)
  - Bouillon (2 of 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 318)
  - Jams, jellies, and perserves (1 of 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 319)
  - Jams, jellies, and perserves (2 of 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 320)
  - [Ball (1)], undated (Box 29, Folder 320A)
  - [Ball (2)], undated (Box 29, Folder 320B)
  - Canned foods (1 of 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 321)
  - Canned foods (2 of 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 322)
  - Salads, undated (Box 29, Folder 323)
  - Salads and dressings, undated (Box 29, Folder 324)
  - Sauces (savory), undated (Box 29, Folder 325)
  - Soups (1 of 3), undated (Box 29, Folder 326)
  - Soups (2 of 3), undated (Box 29, Folder 327)
  - Soups (3 of 3), undated (Box 29, Folder 328)
  - Food processor (1 of 4), undated (Box 30, Folder 329)
  - Food processor (2 of 4), undated (Box 30, Folder 330)
  - Food processor (3 of 4), undated (Box 30, Folder 331)
  - Food processor (4 of 4), undated (Box 30, Folder 332)
  - [Good Housekeeping], undated (Box 30, Folder 332A)
  - [McCalls], undated (Box 30, Folder 332B)
  - Pickling (1 of 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 333)
  - Pickling (2 of 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 334)
  - Gelatine (1 of 3), undated (Box 30, Folder 335)
  - Gelatine (2 of 3), undated (Box 30, Folder 336)
  - Gelatine (3 of 3), undated (Box 30, Folder 337)
  - Electric griddle, undated (Box 30, Folder 338)
  - [USDA], undated (Box 30, Folder 338A)
  - Apples (1 of 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 339)
  - Apples (2 of 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 340)
  - Apples (processed), undated (Box 30, Folder 341)
  - Apples (Washington), undated (Box 30, Folder 342)
  - Apricots, undated (Box 30, Folder 343)
  - Avocados, undated (Box 30, Folder 344)
  - Bananas, undated (Box 30, Folder 345)
  - Berries, undated (Box 30, Folder 346)
  - Cherries, undated (Box 30, Folder 347)
  - Cranberries, undated (Box 30, Folder 348)
  - Citrus (Florida), undated (Box 31, Folder 349)
  - Citrus, undated (Box 31, Folder 350)
  - Dates, undated (Box 31, Folder 351)
  - Dried fruits, undated (Box 31, Folder 352)
  - Figs, undated (Box 31, Folder 353)
  - Grapefruit, undated (Box 31, Folder 354)
  - Grapes, undated (Box 31, Folder 355)
  - Kiwis, undated (Box 31, Folder 356)
  - Lemons and limes, undated (Box 31, Folder 357)
  - Mangos and melons, undated (Box 31, Folder 358)
  - Mince meat, undated (Box 31, Folder 359)
  - Nectarines, undated (Box 31, Folder 360)
  - Oranges, undated (Box 31, Folder 361)
  - Peaches, undated (Box 31, Folder 362)
  - Papayas, undated (Box 31, Folder 363)
  - Pineapples, undated (Box 31, Folder 364)
  - Pears, undated (Box 31, Folder 365)
  - Persimmons, undated (Box 31, Folder 366)
  - Plums, undated (Box 31, Folder 367)
  - Raisins, undated (Box 31, Folder 368)
  - Artichokes and asparagus, undated (Box 32, Folder 369)
  - Beans, undated (Box 32, Folder 370)
  - Beans (dried), undated (Box 32, Folder 371)
  - Soy beans, undated (Box 32, Folder 372)
  - Sauerkraut, undated (Box 32, Folder 373)
  - C vegetables, undated (Box 32, Folder 374)
  - Corn, undated (Box 32, Folder 375)
  - Corn starch, undated (Box 32, Folder 376)
  - Greens, undated (Box 32, Folder 377)
  - Mushrooms (1 of 2), undated (Box 32, Folder 378)
  - Mushrooms (2 of 2), undated (Box 32, Folder 379)
  - Olives, undated (Box 32, Folder 380)
  - Onions, undated (Box 32, Folder 381)
  - Peas, undated (Box 32, Folder 382)
  - Peppers, undated (Box 32, Folder 383)
  - Potatoes (1 of 2), undated (Box 32, Folder 384)
  - Potatoes (2 of 2), undated (Box 32, Folder 385)
  - Pumpkin, undated (Box 32, Folder 386)
  - Sweet potatoes, undated (Box 32, Folder 387)
  - Tomatoes (1 of 2), undated (Box 32, Folder 388)
  - Tomatoes (2 of 2), undated (Box 32, Folder 389)
  - Squash, undated (Box 32, Folder 390)
  - Vegetables (general), undated (Box 32, Folder 391)
  - Vegatables (fresh), undated (Box 32, Folder 392)
  - Watercress, undated (Box 32, Folder 393)
  - Blenders, undated (Box 33, Folder 394)
  - Oster (1 of 2), undated (Box 33, Folder 395)
  - Oster (2 of 2), undated (Box 33, Folder 396)
  - Choppers, undated (Box 33, Folder 397)
  - General Electric, undated (Box 33, Folder 398)
  - Beard, James, undated (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - Joy of Cooking, undated (Box 37, Folder 69)
  - Subseries A: Misc. Printed Material
    - ["1945 Directory of Japanese Americans in New York"] (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - [Burpee's Farm Annual (1888)], undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ["For the Ultimate in Resort and Retirement Living East Hampton"], undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ["Historic Sites U.S."], undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - [Joe Pasternack Materials], undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - ["The Krishna Consciousness Movement is Authorized"], undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - [Pro Arte Choral Pamphlet], undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Series XIV: Oversize
  - The Aluminum Cooking Utensil Company-advertisement, 1932 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Caprilands Herb Farm-herb garden plans and information regarding planting of herb seeds, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Map and guide to Suffolk Co., NY, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Calendars, 1960-1992 (Box 49, Box 50)